[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the European co-principality whose heads of state are the President of France and the Bishop of Urgel.", "correct_answer": "Andorra", "incorrect_answers": ["Vatican City", "San Marino", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The earliest trees on the planet were a type of ferns and are considered to have appeared in which period of Earths geological history?", "correct_answer": "Paleozoic", "incorrect_answers": ["Cenozoic", "Precambrian", "Mesozoic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What star of The Pursuit of Happiness played Christine Thayer, the wife of Cameron Thayer in the 2004 movie Crash?", "correct_answer": "Thandie Newton", "incorrect_answers": ["Angella Bassett", "Christine Johnston", "Christine Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important thing did Einstein do on August 2nd, 1939?", "correct_answer": "He wrote a letter", "incorrect_answers": ["He proved the Theory of Special Relativity", "He found the speed of light", "He proved  E=mc^2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The temperature at the North Pole is higher than the temperature at the South Pole.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many arms does General Grievous have?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "1", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturns rings consist mostly of water ice.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of Stella Adlers brothers was the first Jewish actor to play Adolph Hitler in three movies. Who was he?", "correct_answer": "Luther Adler", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Adler", "Jacob Adler", "Jay Adler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The citizens of which country rejected the idea of joining the EU in 1972 and again in 1994?", "correct_answer": "Norway", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Iceland", "Finland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which constellation did the brightest (Apparent magnitude -9) supernova occur?", "correct_answer": "Lupus", "incorrect_answers": ["Crater", "Antlia", "Hydra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1957 movie Twelve Angry Men what was the occupation of the character, played by Henry Fonda?", "correct_answer": "architect", "incorrect_answers": ["watchmaker", "gym teacher", "salesman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Duality in quantum mechanics is used to describe these two concepts.  The Schrodinger equation is in fact the essence of duality.  Which two concepts are described in duality?", "correct_answer": "particles and waves", "incorrect_answers": ["solids and liquids", "temperature and volume", "liquids and gases"]}]